webmotionuk.co.uk 2012-12-03

# Privacy & Cookies | WebMotionUK

### WebMotionUK is committed to protecting your personal information and other data supplied to us.

This privacy policy explains what information WebMotionUK collects about you, how we collect the information, and how we use your information.

We’re giving you this information as part of our initiative to comply with recent legislation, and to make sure we’re honest and clear about your privacy when using our website.

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this Site and any services we offer via this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site.

### Changes to Privacy Statement

We will process your Personal Information in the way indicated in this Privacy Policy. Over time the way we process your Personal Information may change. We will let you know about changes that may not be obvious to you by publishing them in the Privacy Policy. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of any changes.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy policy, without prior notice to you. If we change the privacy policy, it will be posted to the web site and become effective at the time of posting.

### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit, register or use the services on this Site, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including your name and your contact details. We may also collect information about your use of this Site as well as information about you from the emails, letters and other marketing tools we may use.

### How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We retain access to all personal information that we have collected from you.

When using WebMotionUK you agree that your personal details can be accessed by WebMotionUK staff. No other companies or individuals may access your personal details online through WebMotionUK.

In addition your Personal Information may be used to Contact you for Marketing Purposes.

If you have not consented otherwise, we may provide any of the information we collect to carefully screened third parties to contact you regarding products or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted by these third parties in the future, please contact us and tell us.

If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

We will not otherwise disclose, sell or distribute your information to any third party without your permission unless we are required to do so by law.

### Cookies

Cookies are a perfectly normal part of Internet operations and are also used by WebMotionUK to safely identify you each time you logon and use the site.

When you first visit our site we will automatically generate and send you a cookie (a small text file) this allows us to recognize you on your visits to WebMotionUK. If you require more information on cookies and there functions please visit the following link http://www.cookiecentral.com/.

In the course of serving ads to this site, our third-party advertiser may also place or recognise a unique ‘cookie’ on your browser.

If you decide to disallow cookies you may find that you will not be able to make full use of the features and services on the WebMotionUK website. Payments will not be handled correctly and as a result your order may/will be cancelled.

We will automatically collect data including previous sites visited, your browser type, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site, just generally how you use the site (“User Data”). We use this information to build pictures of how our site is used to allow us to improve the service.

Here’s a list of the main cookies we use, and what we use them for.

Cookie name | Purpose  
---|---  
_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz | 

Google Analytics: These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.

WibiyaLoads, Apache, WibiyaProfile, WibiyaNotification300666 | 

These cookies are set by Wibya, the floating bar in the footer that allows, site search, sharing of information, translation services, and other notifications that we feel are needed for our visitors

If you take the opportunity to ‘share’ WebMotionUK content with friends through social networks – such as Facebook and Twitter – you may be sent cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these cookies, so please check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.  
  
PHPSESSID | This session cookie is required for login purposes and is deleted when you close your browser.  
  
### 3rd Party Cookies

Cookie name | Purpose  
---|---  
_drt_  
id | This cookie is used for banner advertising, located on various parts of the site. Google-owned DoubleClick is for paid advertising on Google.com and allows us to bring aspects of our service to you free of charge.  
  
### User Initiated Contact

If you contact us by telephone or by e-mail asking for assistance we will ask for or take your Personal Information. As well as using your Personal Information to help you, your Personal Information will be used to Contact you for Marketing Purposes.

**NOTE: We will never ask you for your password.**

### Marketing Purposes

If you are a registered user, your Personal Information may be used by us to contact you in writing, by telephone or by e-mail to offer you content, advertisements, products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

You can opt out of receiving contact for Marketing Purposes at any time by amending your details.
